welcome to a new video on opportunities
this week from ravisa temple tree as the
markets have got perched at the top and
most of the stocks have already gone up
there is going to be
very few buying opportunities coming up
in the market now
this week we have a couple of stocks
giving buying opportunities in the
finance sector
there is a catch here finance sector is
in the receiving end
with most of the stocks in the sector
either getting into a tight range or
going down in this condition if we are
getting a buying opportunity from a
stock in the sector it will come with
two conditions a caution and a potential
the caution is that
there is a chance the signal trigger
which we are getting
may not work and it can turn against us
in that case we should have
focus on the stop loss and should be
very alert to get out
on the stop-loss trigger thereby
protecting our capital for future trades
that are going to come the second one
potential
if the trade or the signal after trigger
the stock goes up with momentum that
gives a beautiful opportunity for us to
have gotten at the right time and with
that if the sector is also going up that
gives a multibagger opportunity for the
stock we will make very big gains
today's market
if you have been observing
insurance stocks have been going up for
some time now
this week we have a buying opportunity
from the insurance sector it is icici
general insurance giving a buying
opportunity on trend following approach
we can buy this stock if it is going
above 1645
in the coming week
if you have seen that
sbi life and icic prudential life has
been going up doing good in the market
and along with that hdfc life is also
gaining momentum probably it will have a
buying opportunity in a few days from
now
with that if icici general insurance
also is joining the party
that brings us a little added confidence
that when the micro sector is going up
and we have a stock from that sector
getting a investment opportunity we are
sure that the stock results will also
get carried away carried along with the
micro sector and
with that there is a potential for the
sector itself to go up
so
icici gi is a good buying opportunity
this week while
this said also have a caution in mind
that we should be
concentrating on the stop loss if the
trade goes on strong continue to hold
the position
with the trailing stop loss and maximize
your profits before going further we
would like to share that a couple of
opportunities ideas that we had shared
in our past videos like reliance
hdfc kind of stocks have been doing very
good in the market we believe that
almost all our viewers would have made
fantastic gains from these beautiful
uptrending stocks there are few more
stocks that are available for
opportunities and all of them have been
posted in our discussion group you can
join the discussion group by clicking on
the top link on the description and join
the group where you can have a list of
stocks their entry price stop losses and
targets if it's a swing trade
with insurance to your investment
grow your health wealth with safety and
security happy investment
[Music]
you